<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data><items><count>13</count><item><item_2><id>1</id><name>Remco Wagemakers</name><user_id>337</user_id><first_name>Remco</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Wagemakers</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city/><country/><languages/><job_title_role/><sustainability_interests/><professional_interests/><biography/><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/plugins/ultimate-member/assets/img/default_avatar.jpg</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>2</id><name>Charlotte Perrottey</name><user_id>336</user_id><first_name>Charlotte</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Perrottey</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>she/her</pronouns><city/><country>United States</country><languages>a:2:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:6:"French";}</languages><job_title_role>Other</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>54,67,62,49,63,64</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>45,38,39</professional_interests><biography>15+ years of professional experience in the contemporary art world, working at Christie's auction house and the art advisories Allan Schwartzman, Inc. and Art Agency, Partners. Co-founder of Art to Zero, a NYC-based initiative dedicated to accelerating the visual arts' transition to a decarbonized future, and member organization of PACT (Partners for Arts Climate Targets). Earned an MBA in Sustainability from Bard College.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/336/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>3</id><name>Lia Colabello</name><user_id>335</user_id><first_name>Lia</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Colabello</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>she/her</pronouns><city/><country>United States</country><languages>a:2:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:7:"Spanish";}</languages><job_title_role>Other</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>54,67,58,49,68,52,64,66</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>45,36,111,38,42,110</professional_interests><biography>Lia Colabello develops and manages award-winning sustainability initiatives for organizations, with a focus on reducing single-use plastic, pursuing Climate Neutral and B Corporation certifications, implementing circular economy strategies and engaging entire brand ecosystems in these efforts. She is the Managing Principal of Planet+Purpose Solutions (PPS), a women-led, B Corp Certified boutique consulting practice whose impact is felt globally and spans an immense variety of organizations and industries. By launching organizational sustainability strategies, pursuing third-party certifications, establishing product and packaging stewardship initiatives, building sustainable corporate ethos through employee engagement and aligning clients with cause partners, Lia and her team accelerate solutions to some of the world’s greatest environmental challenges.&#13;
&#13;
Lia was inspired by the power of the intersection of brands and purpose after working around the world with international sports organizations including the PGA TOUR and World Surf League, and later with ocean conservation organizations including the Surfrider Foundation and the 5 Gyres Institute to address the rise of plastic pollution. Originally from the North Shore of O‘ahu in Hawaii, Lia attended the University of Southern California, where she played varsity water polo and graduated with degrees in Broadcast Journalism and Anthropology. She has an MBA from Thunderbird School of Global Management at Arizona State University. Lia lives in Charleston, South Carolina, and loves to explore the ocean and waterways around the Lowcountry with her family.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/335/profile_photo-190x190.png?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>4</id><name>Marie-Claude Mongeon</name><user_id>266</user_id><first_name>Marie-Claude</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Mongeon</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>She/her/elle</pronouns><city/><country>Canada</country><languages>a:3:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:6:"French";i:2;s:7:"Spanish";}</languages><job_title_role>Project Manager</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>56,61,55,58,49</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>45,36,38,42,39</professional_interests><biography>Marie-Claude Mongeon currently works at the Musée d’art contemporain de Montréal.  She previously held various positions at the National Gallery of Canada for over 15 years, where she recently led an ongoing discussion group on greening museum activities. She holds two Bachelor’s degrees from the University of Ottawa, in visual arts and art history, as well as an International Baccalaureate Diploma in natural sciences.  She is currently pursuing a graduate's degree in Corporate Sustainability and Social Responsibility at St. Mike's University at the University of Toronto and a degree in gestion et développement durable at HÉC Montréal.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/266/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>5</id><name>Ekaterina Egorova</name><user_id>139</user_id><first_name>Ekaterina</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Egorova</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city/><country>Russian Federation</country><languages>a:3:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:7:"Russian";i:2;s:7:"Spanish";}</languages><job_title_role>Project Manager</job_title_role><sustainability_interests/><professional_interests/><biography>Founder of Moscow Circular. Circular economy expert.&#13;
&#13;
Ex-partner of the first zero waste shop in Moscow and sustainability agency. Guide of Food System Vision Prize organized by OpenIDEO, Second Muse and the Rockefeller Foundation. OpenIDEO Moscow Chapter organizer. Pioneer and mentor of the Circular economy program by Ellen MacArthur Foundation — From Linear to Circular. In summer of 2020, she founded the Moscow Circular a project, which helps businesses, cities and territories in Russia to switch to a circular economy.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/139/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>6</id><name>Julia Weger</name><user_id>129</user_id><first_name>Julia</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Weger</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city/><country>Austria</country><languages/><job_title_role>Project Manager</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>12,15</sustainability_interests><professional_interests/><biography/><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/129/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>7</id><name>Dmitry Nakoryakov</name><user_id>121</user_id><first_name>Dmitry</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Nakoryakov</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city/><country>Russian Federation</country><languages/><job_title_role>Project Manager</job_title_role><sustainability_interests/><professional_interests/><biography/><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/121/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>8</id><name>Alice Bonnot</name><user_id>68</user_id><first_name>Alice</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Bonnot</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>She/Her</pronouns><city/><country>United Kingdom</country><languages>a:2:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:6:"French";}</languages><job_title_role>Curator</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>67,70,61,58,49,68,65,71,66</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>45,36,37,38,41,42,110,40,39</professional_interests><biography>Alice Bonnot (she/her) is an independent art curator, sustainability consultant, writer and speaker interested in the development of environmentally sustainable curatorial and artistic practices with a drive towards eco solutions. She is the founding director of villa villa, a sustainable and climate-conscious arts programme dedicated to supporting contemporary artists, curators, writers, thinkers, and other cultural and environmental practitioners committed to more ecologically sensitive practices.&#13;
&#13;
As a curator, Alice focuses on developing environmentally respectful exhibitions that address socio-political and environmental issues, as well as broader concerns relating to society. Her current research deals with subjects such as deep ecology, intersectional environmentalism and ecofeminisms. She teaches the course ‘Curating an ecologically sensitive exhibition’ and is regularly invited to speak about art and ecology. &#13;
&#13;
As a sustainability consultant, Alice helps cultural institutions embrace the challenges and opportunities associated with the adoption of sustainable working methods. She worked as an advisor on the development of the upcoming 'Exhibition Ki Book'. Her writing appears regularly in art publications, including Umbigo Magazine, for which she writes as a recurring contributor. She is part of the Green Art Lab Alliance's working group on Future Materials.&#13;
&#13;
&gt;&gt; When she is not working, you can find her connecting with more-than-human beings in nature or embracing the liquid dimensions of her 'ecological self' while surfing in the oceanic currents.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/68/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>9</id><name>Christopher Garthe</name><user_id>57</user_id><first_name>Christopher</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Garthe</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city>Berlin</city><country>Germany</country><languages/><job_title_role>Curator</job_title_role><sustainability_interests/><professional_interests/><biography/><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/57/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>10</id><name>Thierry Leonardi</name><user_id>51</user_id><first_name>Thierry</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Leonardi</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns/><city/><country>France</country><languages/><job_title_role>Curator</job_title_role><sustainability_interests/><professional_interests/><biography/><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/51/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>11</id><name>Douglas Worts</name><user_id>45</user_id><first_name>Douglas</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Worts</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>He/Him/His</pronouns><city/><country>Canada</country><languages>a:1:{i:0;s:7:"English";}</languages><job_title_role>Researcher</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>54,67,70,61,55,58,51,62,49,59,63,57,60,50,71,52</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>43,45,36,46,42</professional_interests><biography>I've been a museum professional for over 40 years. My experience, (primarily at the Art Gallery of Ontario, in Toronto, Canada), focused on experimental exhibit development in an art museum setting, as well as on audience research. I was one of the founding directors of the Visitor-Studies Association. One of my most interesting areas of research has been in 'visitor-based creativity' - specifically creativity generated by visitors as they engage with artworks. &#13;
&#13;
For the past 25 years, my research, publishing and teaching has been focused on the potential of museums to play a meaningful role in fostering cultural adaptation and change in a fast-transforming world. Central to this work has been the need to embrace something called "systems thinking" - which involves understanding how multiple, interdependent systems function together in dynamic balance. For museums to become catalysts of cultural adaptation, it is important to be able to use systems thinking to understand current trends and to generate effective, innovative interventions in the living culture.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/45/profile_photo-190x190.jpeg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>12</id><name>Kim Kraczon</name><user_id>33</user_id><first_name>Kim</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Kraczon</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>she/her</pronouns><city/><country>Netherlands</country><languages>a:2:{i:0;s:7:"English";i:1;s:6:"German";}</languages><job_title_role>Conservator</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>67,49,68,65,64,69,66</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>47,45,36,111,38,41,39</professional_interests><biography>After finishing a second bachelor’s degree in the Conservation of Modern Materials and Technical Cultural Heritage at the Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft in Berlin, I worked for 8 years as the resident conservator at Studio Olafur Eliasson in Berlin, Germany where I was responsible for repairs and conservation treatments of artworks, as well as developing sustainable strategies for art production and packing systems. I’m currently pursuing my master’s degree in the Conservation and Restoration of Contemporary Art at the University of Amsterdam, where I intend to focus on the use of recycled materials and emerging bioplastics and biomaterials in contemporary art. Aside from my role as a Ki Coach in Ki Culture, I also serve as the Director of Materials and am at the helm of the Materials Ki Book. I additionally lead Gallery Climate Coalition’s Packaging and Materials Research Committee and am one of the founding members of the Berlin branch of the Gallery Climate Coalition.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/33/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2><item_2><id>13</id><name>Nicole Smith</name><user_id>14</user_id><first_name>Nicole</first_name><user_type>coach</user_type><last_name>Smith</last_name><created>2022-07-15 14:39:10</created><modified>2022-07-15 14:39:26</modified><permalink/><pronouns>she/her</pronouns><city/><country>United States</country><languages>a:1:{i:0;s:7:"English";}</languages><job_title_role>Conservator</job_title_role><sustainability_interests>56,70,61,58,51,49,59,65,60,50,52</sustainability_interests><professional_interests>45,36,38,42,39</professional_interests><biography>Nicole has spent her career as a driving force for positive change in diversity, equity, accessibility and inclusion at museums with the principal belief that museums should be for everyone. Through over 15 years of  museum experience, Nicole has advocated for this belief in her work with visitor experience, membership, communications, programming and most importantly sustainability and accessibility. &#13;
&#13;
Through her work, Nicole has helped museums navigate diversity, equity accessibility  and inclusion work. Her efforts have been recognized with institutional awards at the local and national level. In 2017, Nicole was recognized as an Emerging Leader for Arts and Disability by  the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts. &#13;
&#13;
Nicole continues to serve and advocate through her current roles including: As the founder of Before Thought  where she provides consulting services that focuses on inclusive accessibility practices for people with disabilities in the cultural sector. And as the Co-Director of Social Sustainability at Ki Culture, a non-profit that advocates for museums as spaces that benefit people, places and the planet.</biography><profile_pic>https://kiportdev.wpenginepowered.com/wp-content/uploads/ultimatemember/14/profile_photo-190x190.jpg?1657895952</profile_pic></item_2></item></items></data>
